{
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Assyrian king Sennacherib&#039;s destruction of Babylon in 689 BCE was viewed as a triumph by other Assyrian citizens.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Tennis was once known as Racquetball.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The capital of the US State Ohio is the city of Chillicothe.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The Hundred Years&#039; War was fought for more than a hundred years.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
}